[Music]
Hello Kapoor ji, many congratulations on your new house.
You have built a beautiful house.
Hi
son, please help us a little so that
our dream of owning a house can also be fulfilled.
Honestly, ICICI Home Finance
Company made it easy to buy a house. They
helped us a lot in buying a house. They got us a
home loan at a good and reasonable interest rate. They
also helped us avail the benefits of the Credit Linked Subsidy Scheme under the Pradhan Mantri Awas Yojana. They
kept the documents to a minimum and also
helped with the paperwork. Everything is digital and transparent.
This means that with the help of ICICI Home Finance Company,
my big dream can be fulfilled.
Of course, let's celebrate this.
Thank you.
[Music]
Excuse me, Alok Verma ji, I met you. Thank you. Hello,
I am Alok Verma. Tell me, can I help you?
Kapoor ji told me about you. He was
very complimentary about how
you helped him in buying a new house.
So I thought I should also meet you and
understand how you can help me. Yes, we will
definitely help you. You did
not tell me your name. Sanjeev Trivedi ji, let's
sit and talk.
This branch is better than other financial institutions.  It
is quite different, I mean in looks also
and this face to face conversation that we are having, there is a
lot of intimacy. Thank you.
So tell me more about ICICI Home Finance Company.
See, we are a
part of ICICI Group. Home
Finance Company. Now understand that ICICI
Home Finance Company is the home of the customer's future and
dream needs. We
suggest our products to the customers as per their needs. After that, the
customers can
choose any of those products as per their dreams and needs. Be it
big or small dreams, we
fully support the customers in fulfilling them.
You can see for yourself
[Music]